Preliminary Guide to the I. Richard Savage Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Series I, 1955-1989; 27 linear feet (23 boxes)
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Langley, Richmond W. (Box 8)
    - Lord, Frederic M. (Box 8)
    - Lorrie, James H. (Box 8)
    - Loynes, Robert (Box 8)
    - Lubin, Ardie (Box 8)
    - Ludwick, John C., and Elkins, Thomas A. (Box 8)
    - Lukacs, Eugene (Box 8)
    - Lusted, Lee B. (Box 8)
    - Lyon, Mary F. (Box 8)
    - M (Box 8)
    - McClosky, Herbert (Box 8)
    - McCormack, Robert L. (Box 8)
    - McDonald, Bruce J. (Box 8)
    - McDonald, James E., and Green, Christine R. (Box 8)
    - MacEachern, Donald G. (Box 8)
    - McFarland, David D. (Box 8)
    - McFeely, Franklin S., and Freund, J. E. (Box 8)
    - McGilchrist, C. A. (Box 8)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company (Box 8)
    - MacKinnon, William J. (Box 8)
    - Macmillan Company (Box 8)
    - McNeil, Donald R. (Box 8)
    - McWilliams, Ralph (Box 8)
    - Madow, William G. (Box 8)
    - Mainland, Donald (Box 8)
    - Makela, Benjamin R. (Box 8)
    - Malick, Henrick J. (Box 8)
    - Mallios, William S. (Box 8)
    - Mandel, John (Box 8)
    - Mann, Nancy R. (Box 8)
    - Manski, Charles F. (Box 8)
    - Mantel, Nathan (Box 8)
    - March, James G. (Box 8)
    - Mardia, K. V. (Box 8)
    - Margolin, Barry (Box 8)
    - Maris, Ronald (Box 8)
    - Maritz, J. S. (Box 8)
    - Marshall, Stanley (Box 8)
    - Martin, Donald C. (Box 8)
    - Martin, J. David (Box 8)
    - Martin, Margaret E. (Box 8)
    - Martin-Lof, Anders (Box 8)
    - Martz, Harry F., Jr., and Krutchkoff, Richard G. (Box 8)
    - Massey, Frank (Box 8)
    - Mathai, A. M. (Box 8)
    - Matras, Judah (Box 8)
    - Matusita, Kameo (Box 8)
    - Maurice, Rita J. (Box 8)
    - Mayhew, Bruce H. (Box 8)
    - Maynes, E Scott (Box 8)
    - Meeter, Duane (Box 8)
    - Mehta, J. S. (Box 8)
    - Meier, Paul, and Kaplan, E. L (Box 8)
    - Merrill, W. Jay, Jr. (Box 9)
    - Methodology, books on statistical (Box 9)
    - Meyer, David E. (Box 9)
    - Midzuno, Hiroshi (Box 9)
    - Mielke, Paul W., Jr. (Box 9)
    - Mikulski, Piotr W. (Box 9)
    - Milledgeville, Georgia, visit to Georgia College (Box 9)
    - Miller, Rupert G., Jr. (Box 9)
    - Milly, (?) (Box 9)
    - Milton, Roy C. (Box 9)
    - Minton, Paul D. (Box 9)
    - Mitra, Sujit Kumar (Box 9)
    - Mohanty, S. G. (Box 9)
    - Mohring, Herbert (Box 9)
    - Mood, Alexander M. (Box 9)
    - Moore, Bobbie Iris (Box 9)
    - Moore, L. T. (Box 9)
    - Moore, P. G. (Box 9)
    - Moranda, Paul B. (Box 9)
    - Morreale, M. V. (Box 9)
    - Morris, Charles (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Donald F. (Box 9)
    - Moser, Claus (Box 9)
    - Moses, Lincoln E. (Box 9)
    - Mosteller, Frederick (Box 9)
    - Murty, V. N. (Box 9)
    - Mustafi, Chandan K. (Box 9)
    - Myers, James C. (Box 9)
    - N (Box 9)
    - Nagnur, B. N. (Box 9)
    - Nahinsky, Irwin D. (Box 9)
    - Naik, Umesh D. (Box 9)
    - Nam, Charles, Sobel, (?), and Savage, I. R. (Box 9)
    - Nam, Jun-mo (Box 9)
    - Narayana, T. V. (Box 9)
    - Natarajan, S. (Box 9)
    - National Academy of Sciences
      - National Research Council (NRC) Advisory Committee to Army Research Office (Durham) [ARO(D)] (Box 9)
      - NRC Committee on Statistics, Division of Mathematics (Box 9)
    - National Research Council (Box 9)
      General
      see also: box 1
    - National Science Foundation
      - Correspondence (from Florida State University and Yale University) (Box 9)
      - Proposal (Box 9)
      - Reviews of proposals (Box 9)
      - Science Development Program (SDP) Advisory Committee (Box 9)
    - Natrella, Mary G. (Box 9)
    - Naval Research Logistics Quarterly (Box 9)
    - Nederlof, M. H. (Box 9)
    - Nelson, (?) (Box 9)
    - Nerlove, Marc (Box 9)
    - Neter, John (Box 9)
    - Nettheim, Nigel F. (Box 9)
    - Newcombe, Theodore Mead (Box 9)
    - Newell, David (Box 9)
    - Neyman, Jerzy (Box 9)
    - Nichol, E. Sterling (Box 9)
    - Nicholson, W. L. (Box 9)
    - Noether, Gottfried E. (Box 9)
    - Nonparametric Institute (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Nonparametric Symposium, 1st International (Box 9)
    - Novick, Melvin (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - O (Box 9)
    - Odeh, Robert H (Box 9)
    - Odell, Patrick, Newman, T. G., and Speed, M. (Box 9)
    - Oehlert, Gary (Box 9)
    - Office of Naval Research (Box 9)
    - Ogawa, Junjiro (Box 9)
    - Oldman, Oliver (Box 9)
    - Olds, Edwin G. (Box 9)
    - Olkin, Ingram (Box 9)
    - Olsen, H., (Office of Naval Research) (Box 9)
    - O'Reagan, Robert T. (Box 9)
    - Ostle, Bernard, and Steck, George P. (Box 9)
    - Owen, Donald B. (Box 9)
    - P (Box 9)
    - Pachares, James (Box 9)
    - Palmer, D. S. (Box 9)
    - Panofsky, (?) (Box 9)
    - Paredes, John H. (Box 9)
    - Park, (?) (Box 9)
    - Parrish, Gene B. (Box 9)
    - Parzen, E. ("Manny") (Box 9)
    - Patel, Jagdish K. (Box 9)
    - Patel, Kantilal M. (Box 9)
    - Patil, G. P. (Box 9)
    - Patin, John R. (Box 9)
    - Payne, W. H., and Gibbons, C. J. (Box 9)
    - Pearson, E. S. (Box 9)
    - Perisho, Clarence R. (Box 9)
    - Petrasovits, Andres (Box 9)
    - Pennock, Jean L., and Jaeger, Carol M. (Box 9)
    - Phillips, David P., and Chase, Gary A. (others in here!) (Box 9)
    - Physical Chemistry 104 (Box 9)
    - Pierson, W. J. (Box 9)
    - Pike, Eugene W. (Box 9)
    - Pirie, Walter R. (Box 9)
    - Practical work (Box 9)
    - Praetz, Peter D. (Box 9)
    - Pratt, John W. (Box 9)
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Press, S. James (Box 9)
    - Preston, Glenn W. (Box 9)
    - Promotion and tenure. Department of Statistics, Florida State University: Policies (Box 9)
    - Proschan, Frank (Box 9)
    - Puri, Madan Lal (Box 9)
    - Q (Box 10)
    - Quade, Dana (Box 10)
    - Qualifying Exam, Department of Statistics. Yale University (Box 10)
    - R (Box 10)
    - Radner, Roy (Box 10)
    - Raghavachari, M. (Box 10)
    - Raghavachari, R. (Box 10)
    - Raghavarao, D., Sodhi, (?), and Singh, (?) (Box 10)
    - Raiffa, Howard (Box 10)
    - Rainio, Kullervo (Box 10)
    - Ramalakshmi, Jandhyala (Box 10)
    - Randles, Ronald H. (Box 10)
    - Randomization (subject file) (Box 10)
    - Ranganathan, J. (Box 10)
    - Rao, A. Vijaya (Box 10)
    - Rao, B. L. S. Prakasa (in A. V. Rao folder) (Box 10)
    - Rao, J. N. K., and Ostle, Bertrand (Box 10)
    - Rao, U. V. Ramamohana (Box 10)
    - Rasmussen, Uttara (Box 10)
    - Redfern, Philip (Box 10)
    - Reid, Charles Edward, Jr. (Box 10)
    - Resnikoff, George J. (Box 10)
    - Riceman, David (Box 10)
    - Richter, Donald L. (Box 10)
    - Rider, Paul R. (Box 10)
    - Riecken, Henry W. (Box 10)
    - Riedwyl, Hans (Box 10)
    - Riffenburgh, Robert H. (Box 10)
    - Rizvi, M. Haseeb (Box 10)
    - Roberts, Harry V. (Box 10)
    - Robson, D. S. (Box 10)
    - Rochester, University of: visit (Box 10)
    - Roeloffs, Robert (Box 10)
    - Roff, Merrill (Box 10)
    - Rogers, Grover L. (Box 10)
    - Ronald Press Company (Box 10)
    - Rose, Marshall (Box 10)
    - Roselle, David P. (Box 10)
    - Rosen, Harvey (Box 10)
    - Rosenblatt, Joan R. (Box 10)
    - Rosenblatt, Murray (Box 10)
    - Ross, Sheldon M. (Box 10)
    - Rovetta, Charles A. (Box 10)
    - Roy, S. N. (Box 10)
    - Royal Statistical Society (Box 10)
    - Rubin, Herman (Box 10)
    - Rudy, Norman (Box 10)
    - Rush, N. Orwin (Box 10)
    - Russell, C. Bradley (Box 10)
    - Rustagi, Jagdish (Box 10)
    - Rutemiller, Herbert C. (Box 10)
    - Rutherford, J. R. (Box 10)
    - Ryan, Frank J. (Box 10)
    - S (Box 10)
    - Sachs, Robert (Box 10)
    - Saffran, Bernard (Box 10)
    - Saleh, A. K. Ehsanes (Box 10)
    - Saleh, E. and Scott (Box 10)
    - Samaniego, Francisco J. (Box 10)
    - Sampson, Allan R. (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Samuel-Cahn, Ester (Box 10)
    - Sarhan, A. E. (Box 10)
    - Sarndal, Carl-Erik (Box 10)
    - Sauerlander, Owan H. (Box 10)
    - Savage, I. Richard (Box 10)
    - Savage, Jean (Mrs. Leonard J. Savage) (Box 10)
    - Savage, Leonard J. ("Jimmie") (Box 10)
    - Savage, Sam L. (Box 11)
    - Saxena, Krishna Murari Lal (Box 11)
    - Schaefer, Ray E., and Bricker, Jacob L. (Box 11)
    - Schlaifer, Robert (Box 11)
    - Schmetterer, L. (Box 11)
    - Schmookler, Jacob (Box 11)
    - Schnee, Edward (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Schneider, John T. (Box 11)
    - Schnore, Leo F. (Box 11)
    - Schram, John Michael (Box 11)
    - Schultz, Vincent (Box 11)
    - Schwager, Steven (Box 11)
    - Schwinden, James (Box 11)
    - Sclove, Stanley L., and van Ryzin, J. (Box 11)
    - Scotton, Carol M. (Box 11)
    - Seal, K. C. (Box 11)
    - Search Committee in Biostatistics, Department of Statistics. Yale University (Box 11)
    - Seeley, John R. (Box 11)
    - Seiden, Esther (Box 11)
    - Sen, Pranab Kumar (Box 11)
    - Sengupta, J. K., and Sanyal, B. C. (Box 11)
    - Serfling, Robert J. (Box 11)
    - Sethuraman, Jayaram (Box 11)
    - Shah, K. R. (Box 11)
    - Sharma, P. C. (Box 11)
    - Shaugnessey, Gerald (Box 11)
    - Shchigolev, B. M. (Box 11)
    - Sheps, Mindel C. (Box 11)
    - Shimi, I. N. (Box 11)
    - Shimkin, Demitri B. (Box 11)
    - Shrikhande, S. S. (Box 11)
    - Shorak, Roger A. (Box 11)
    - Shubik, Martin (Box 11)
    - Siegel, Jacob S. (Box 11)
    - Siegelman, Philip (Box 11)
    - Sielken, Robert Lewis (Box 11)
    - Sierra Club (Box 11)
    - Simon, (?) (Box 11)
    - Simon, Julian L. (Box 11)
    - SIMS (SIAM Institute for Mathematics and Society) (Box 11)
    - Singh, Chanchal (Box 11)
    - Sirken, Monroe G. (Box 11)
    - Skibinsky, Morris (Box 11)
    - Skvoretz, John V. (Box 11)
    - Slakter, Malcom J. (Box 11)
    - Smith, Armand V., Jr. (Box 11)
    - Smith, Barnard E., and Vemuganti, Ramakrishna (Box 11)
    - Smith, Furman H. (Box 11)
    - Smith, George E. J., and Mehra, K. L. (Box 11)
    - Smith, Jean (Box 11)
    - Smith, Wayne E. (Box 11)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Box 11)
    - Sobel, Milton (Box 11)
    - Social Forces (Box 11)
    - Social Indicators (Box 11)
    - Solomon, Daniel L. (Box 11)
    - Solomon, Herbert (Box 11)
    - Somers, Robert H. (Box 11)
    - Somerville, Paul N. (Box 11)
    - Sorum, Marilyn, and Buehler, Robert J. (Box 11)
    - Spangler, Miller B. (Box 11)
    - Spencer, Bruce (Box 11)
    - Spilerman, Seymour (Box 11)
    - Spindler, George D. (Box 11)
    - Spitzer, Frank (Box 11)
    - Spoeri, Randall K. (Box 11)
    - Sprehe, J. Timothy (Box 11)
    - Spuhler, J. N. (Box 11)
    - Srikantan, K. S. (Box 11)
    - Srivastava, M. S. (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Srivastava, Surendra K. (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Statistics 41a, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 110 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 118b: Asymptotic Statistics (Box 12)
    - Statistics 157 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 210, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Statistics/Mathematics 241a/ Statistics 541a (Box 12)
    - Statistics 242b, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 242b/542b/ Mathematics 242b, 1988 (Box 12)
    - F-310 (???) (Box 12)
    - Statistics 451 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 520 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 521 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 522 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 524 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 525 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 526 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 545: Sequential Analysis (Box 12)
    - Statistics 549 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 610a, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 621 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 625a: Case Studies, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 625 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 626b: Practical Work (Box 12)
    - Statistics 641 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 602b, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Statistics 610 (Box 13)
    - Statistics 641-642 (Box 13)
    - Statistics 642 (Box 13)
    - Statistics 644 (Box 13)
    - Statistics 652a (Box 13)
    - Statistics 660a, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Statistics 661 (Douglas Wolfe) (2 folders), 1970, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Statistics 685b, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Statistical Center, University of Minnesota (Box 13)
    - Statistics, Department of, Advisory Committee. University of Minnesota (Box 13)
    - Statistics, Department of, Minutes. Florida State University (Box 13)
    - Statistics: linear models (subject file) (Box 13)
    - Statistics: nonparametric (subject file) (Box 13)
    - Statistics in the public interest (subject file) (Box 13)
    - Steck, G. P., and Owen, D. B. (Box 13)
    - Steel, Robert G. D. (Box 13)
    - Sten, Walter G., and Edwards, David N. (Box 13)
    - Sterling, Theodor D. (Box 13)
    - Steyn, H. S. (Box 13)
    - Stigler, Stephen M. (Box 13)
    - Stinchcombe, Arthur L. (Box 13)
    - Stoker, D. J. (Box 13)
    - Stone, Mervyn (Box 13)
    - Straf, Miron L. (Box 13)
    - Stuart, Alan (Box 13)
    - Sukhatme, B. V., and Mokkhaves, Mallika (Box 13)
    - Sullo, Pasquale (Box 13)
    - Summer Institute (NSF Summer Institute for College Teachers),Florida State University, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Sundrum, R. M. (Box 13)
    - Suppes, Patrick C. (Box 13)
    - Suzuki, Giitiro (Box 13)
    - Szekely, Gabor (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - T (Box 13)
    - Taha, Mohamed A. H. (Box 13)
    - Takacs, Lajos (Box 13)
    - Tan, Wai-Yuan (Box 13)
    - Taneja, V. S. (Box 13)
    - Taubman, Stephen (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Howard M. (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Michael (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Robert Lee (Box 13)
    - Teichroew, Dan (Box 13)
    - Tenenbein. Aaron (Box 13)
    - Thacker, Jerrold G. (Box 13)
    - Thall, Peter F. (Box 13)
    - Theil, Henri (Box 13)
    - Thirty-Niners Dining Club (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Donald G., and Gart, J. G. (Box 14)
    - Thompson, D. J., and Kodlin, D. (Box 14)
    - Thompson, James R. (Box 14)
    - Thompson, Rory (Box 14)
    - Thompson, William A. (Box 14)
    - Tiku, M. L. (Box 14)
    - Tingey, Henry B. (Box 14)
    - Tintner, Gerhard (Box 14)
    - Todorovic, Peter (Box 14)
    - Tong, Yung Liang (Box 14)
    - Toulouse, Julian H. (Box 14)
    - Tripathi, T. P. (Box 14)
    - Tsai, Hui-Liang (Box 14)
    - Tsao, Chia Kuei (Box 14)
    - Tsutakawa, R. K., and Meier, Paul (Box 14)
    - Tukey, John W. (Box 14)
    - Tullock, Gordon (Box 14)
    - Turner, William D. (Box 14)
    - T, U, V (Box 14)
    - U (Box 14)
    - Undergraduate Program, Department of Statistics, Undergraduate Program in Statistics, Probability, Operations Research. Florida State University (Box 14)
    - University of Chicago Press (Box 14)
    - University of Maryland (Box 14)
    - University of Michigan (Box 14)
    - University of Rochester (Box 14)
    - Uthoff, Vincent A. (Box 14)
    - Uzawa, H. (Box 14)
    - V (Box 14)
    - van Belle, Gerald (Box 14)
    - Vancouver and Montreal, International Congress of Mathematics, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Venzke, Gene A., and Barr, Donald R. (Box 14)
    - Villars, D. S. (Box 14)
    - Vinod, H. D. (Box 14)
    - Vishnuvajjala, Lakshmi (Box 14)
    - Visiting (NSF Senior Postdoctoral Fellowship, which IRS took at the Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences.), 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - Vogt, (?) (Box 14)
    - Volbeda, Ir. H. K. (Box 14)
    - W (Box 14)
    - Wackerly, Dennis D. (Box 14)
    - Wadley, F. M. (Box 14)
    - Wadsworth Publishing Company, Inc. (Box 14)
    - Wagner, Stephen S. (Box 14)
    - Waikar, Vasant B. (Box 14)
    - Wald, Abraham (Box 14)
    - Wallace, David L. (Box 14)
    - Waller, Ray A., and Duncan, David B. (Box 14)
    - Wallis, W. Allen (Box 14)
    - Walsh, John E. (Box 14)
    - Wan, Jim-Yau (Box 14)
    - Wang, Ying Yao (Box 14)
    - Want, J. K., and Kabe, D. G. (Box 14)
    - Warsaw (International Statistical Institute, 40th Session), 1975 (Box 14)
    - Washburn, (?) (Box 14)
    - Waxenberg, Sheldon E. (Box 14)
    - Way, Florine L. (Box 14)
    - Webster, Murray. Jr. (Box 14)
    - W. B. Saunders Company (Box 14)
    - Weed, Harrison D. (Box 14)
    - Weiler, H. (Box 14)
    - Weiner, Sidney (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Weingarten, Harry (Box 14)
    - Wesler, Oscar (Box 14)
    - White, Harrison C. (Box 14)
    - White, John S. (Box 14)
    - Whiting, (?) (Box 14)
    - Whitney, D. Ransom (Box 14)
    - Wiggins, Alvin D. (Box 14)
    - Wilber, George (Box 14)
    - Wilcoxon, Frank (Box 14)
    - Wilensky, (?) (Box 14)
    - Wilks, S.S. (Box 14)
    - Williams, James R. (Box 14)
    - Willis, Richard H. (Box 14)
    - Wilson, O. Meredith (Box 14)
    - Wilson, Thomas P. (Box 14)
    - Windham, Bernard M. (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Winkler, Robert L. (Box 14)
    - Winslow, Robert W. (Box 14)
    - Wise, M. E. (Box 14)
    - Witt, Ward (Box 14)
    - Wold, Herman (Box 14)
    - Wolfowitz, Jacob (Box 14)
    - Wolpe, J. (Box 14)
    - Wood, John T. (Box 14)
    - Woodruff, Ralph S. (Box 14)
    - Woodworth, George (Box 14)
    - Wrighton, R. F. (Box 14)
    - W - X - Y - Z (Box 15)
    - X - Y - Z (Box 15)
    - Y (Box 15)
    - Yale Club of New York (Box 15)
    - Yale University (various topics) (Box 15)
    - Yen, Elizabeth H. (Box 15)
    - Youden, W. J. (Box 15)
    - Young, Shirley (Box 15)
    - Z (Box 15)
    - Zacks, Shelley (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Zeigler, R. K. (Box 15)
    - Zeisel, Hans (Box 15)
    - Zelditch, Morris, Jr. (Box 15)
    - Zelterman, Daniel (Box 15)
    - Zuckerman, Harriet (Box 15)
  - Projects
    - AIDS (grant awarded by National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases) (Box 15)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science
      - General (Box 15)
      - Committee on Nominations (Box 15)
      - Section U: Nominating Committee (Box 15)
    - AHSME (American High School Mathematics Examination; sponsored by ASA. No folder) (Box 15)
    - American Statistical Association
      - Ad Hoc Committee on the Disabled in Statistics (Box 15)
      - 150 Advisory Committee (Box 15)
      - War and peace (subject file; mainly the ASA's Ad Hoc Committee on Statistics and National Security)
        - Agenda
        - Business (Box 15)
        - Charge (?) (Box 15)
        - Economics, Manpower, and Wargaming (Box 15)
        - Fellowship for project (Box 15)
        - INF 89 (?) (Box 15)
        - Membership (Box 15)
        - Membership (cont'd?) Miscellaneous (Box 15)
        - New Orleans (luncheon meeting) (Box 15)
        - Program Committee (Box 15)
    - Boen, Jim (Box 15)
    - Calculus, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Census, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences (Box 15)
    - Current Index to Statistics Topics (Box 15)
    - Erlbaum, Lawrence/Lawrence Erlbaum Associates, Inc., Publishers (Box 15)
    - Fisher Lecture/R. A. Fisher Award (Box 15)
    - General disabled complaints (Box 16)
    - Handicapped: demography (Box 16)
    - Human Exposure Assessment Network (Box 16)
    - Invoices/Requests (Box 16)
    - Los Alamos project: "Statistics in a Hostile Environment" (Box 16)
    - LSS (?) (Box 16)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) (Box 16)
    - National Bureau of Standards report (Box 16)
    - New Haven, Mayor's Committee on the Handicapped (Box 16)
    - The New Palgrave: A Dictionary of Economic Theory and Doctrine
      - "Random Variables" (Box 16)
      - "Savage, Leonard J." (Box 16)
    - New York University (NYU) Medical Center (Box 16)
    - "Nonparametric and Robust Aspects of Bayesian Statistical Analysis" (Box 16)
    - "Nonparametric Statistics and Microcosms" (Box 16)
    - Pratt, John w. (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - "Propagation of Error" (Box 16)
    - Recording for the Blind (Box 16)
    - Roper Center Advisory Committee (part of the Roper Center at Yale) (Box 16)
    - Savage, Leonard J.: University of Michigan (Box 16)
    - Science (pub. by American Association for the Advancement of Science) (Box 16)
    - Societal Institute of the Mathematical Sciences (SIMS) (Box 16)
    - Spring 1989 (?) (Box 16)
    - Summer 1986 (?) (Box 16)
    - Summer 1987 (?) (Box 16)
    - Summer 1989 (?) (empty) (Box 16)
    - Yale University
      - Director of Undergraduate Studies, Department of Statistics (Box 16)
      - Resource Office for Students and Employees with Disabilities (Box 16)
      - War and peace (Box 16)
  - Published Papers
    - "Bibliography of Nonparametric Statistics and Related Topics", 1953 (Box 17)
    - "Proof That Sufficient Statistics Do Not Exist for the Parameters of the Extreme-Value Distribution: Appendix A"; with Lieblein (?), 1954 (Box 17)
    - "Tables of the Expected Value of 1/X for Positive Bernoulli and Poisson Variables"; with Grab, Edwin L., 1954 March (Box 17)
    - "Problem II - Suggested Solution"; with Chernoff, Herman, 1954 (Box 17)
    - "Tables of Inverses of Finite Segments of the Hilbert Matrix"; with Lukacs, Eugene, 1954 (Box 17)
    - "Cycling", 1956 (Box 17)
    - "Contributions to the Theory of Rank Order Statistics: The Two-Sample Case", 1956 (Box 17)
    - "Contributions to the Theory of Rank Order Statistics: The 'Trend' Case", 1957 (Box 17)
    - Chernoff-Savage Theorem (?), 1957 (Box 17)
    - "On the Independence of Tests of Randomness and Other Hypotheses", 1957 (Box 17)
    - Nonparametric Methods in Statistics, by D. A. S. Fraser: published review, 1957 (Box 17)
    - "Expected Values of the Rank Order Statistics from a Normal Population for N=21"; with Z. Govindarajulu (unpublished research), 1958 (Box 17)
    - "Asymptotic Normality and Efficiency of Certain Nonparametric Test Statistics"; with Chernoff, Herman, 1958 (Box 17)
    - "Nonparametric Statistics"; published review of Nonparametric Statistics for the Behavioral Sciences, by Sidney Siegel, 1958 (Box 17)
    - "A Production Model and Continuous Sampling Plan", 1959 (Box 17)
    - Experimental Designs in Industry, ed. by Victor Chew: published review, 1959 (Box 17)
    - "Contributions to the Theory of Rank Order Statistics: The One-Sample Case", 1959 (Box 17)
    - "Contributions to the Theory of Rank Order Statistics: Computation Rules for Probabilities of Rank Orders", 1960 (Box 17)
    - "Contributions to the Field of Rank Order Statistics: The Two-Sample Censored Case"; with Rao, U. V. B., and Sobel, M., 1960 (Box 17)
    - "The Prophylactic Value of Long-Term Anticoagulant Therapy"; with Thomes, A. Boyd, and Scallen, Raymond W., 1960 (Box 17)
    - "Starting a Control Chart"; with Proschan, F., 1960 (Box 17)
    - "A Statistical Model of the Gross Analysis of Transaction Flows"; with Deutsch, Karl, 1960 (Box 17)
    - "Probility Ineequalities of the Tchebycheff Type" (Box 17)
    - "Value of Long-Term Anticoagulant Therapy in Coronary Disease"; with Thomes, A. Boyd, and Scallen, Raymond W., 1961 (Box 17)
    - "A Quick Test for Locating Peaks in Some Time Series Problems", 1962 (Box 17)
    - "Test of Peak Values in Physiopathologic Time Series"; with Rao, M. M., and Halberg, F., 1962 (Box 17)
    - "Nonparametric Bibliography", 1962 (Box 17)
    - "Surveillance Problems", 1962 (Box 17)
    - "Mills' Ratio for Multivariate Normal Distributions", 1962 (Box 17)
    - Bibliography of Statistical Literature, by Maurice G. Kendall and Alison G. Doig: published review, 1963 (Box 17)
    - Probability Theory and Mathematical Statistics, Third Edition, by Marek Fisz: published review, 1963 (Box 17)
    - "Contributions to the Theory of Rank Order Statistics: Applications of Lattice Theory", 1964 (Box 17)
    - "Surveillance Problems: Poisson Models with Noise", 1964 (Box 17)
    - "Survey of Nonparametric Statistics", 1964 (Box 17)
    - "Characteristic Functions of Stochastic Integrals and Reliability Theory"; with Antelman, Gordon R., 1965 (Box 17)
    - "Finite Stopping Time and Finite Expected Stopping Time"; with Savage, Leonard J., 1965 (Box 17)
    - Handbook of Nonparametric Statistics, by J. E. Walsh: published review, 1965 (Box 17)
    - "Notes on Sedimentation Models", 1965 (Box 17)
    - Nonparametric Trend Analysis, by George A. Ferguson: published review, 1965 (Box 17)
    - "Surveillance Problems: Wiener Processes"; with Antelman, Gordon R., 1965 (Box 17)
    - "Fine Structure of the Ordering of Probabilities of Rank Orders in the Two-Sample Case"; with Sobel, M., and Woodworth, George, 1966 (Box 17)